Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem!
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Yes, we sank one ship.
Just one, belonging to some.
I'm Clay, a Baroque works agent.
The other ship was able to get away.
So you let them escape.
To think that I fell
for such a cheap trick.
Running away is what they do best.
Miss Hina, watch out!
But it's so infuriating.
Hina's angry.
Anger at your own incompetence?
No, that's not it.
Whoa!
Outstanding!
Cage Cage Fruit is intense!
She has the power to bind any
part of the body she touches!
That's a skill!
Come on, say it!
Say the killer line just one time!
What the hell did you do to me?
I'm mad at you, Smoker. Hina's mad.
Care to elaborate on that?
It's just that you actually seem to be
happy about the Straw Hats getting away.
Hmm? Me?
Why would I be?
Who knows?
At which point my dearest Vivi
said to me in a very formal manner,
I have something important to
talk with you about, Daddy.
I mean, Father.
At that moment, I remember thinking for
myself, King or no, it makes no difference.
It's no man gives up
the title daddy watching
children grow is a bittersweet experience.
Try as I might I cannot accept your death!
I can't even shed one tear.
Why is that, old friend?
Cutting fire!
Oh, it's so funny, Toto.
You've been laughing
ever since the speech.
Yeah, let us in on the joke, old man,
because right now we're in the dark.
It's a secret, but trust
me, guys, it's a good one.
You're not making any sense.
Now have a good journey, Luffy.
You're welcome to drink
Yuba's water any time.
All right, that's enough join!
There's work to be done.
Dig the bell, dig!
Okay, okay.
Does anyone have a clue who
Princess Phoebe was talking to?
Nah, but who really cares anyway?
Yeah, what she said makes us happy.
And it's our duty to respond
to it. She's right. Well said.
Even though we're simply peasants.
Speak for yourself, peasant.
As expected, Elobarna seems
to be in bad shape. Perfect.
We should go there.
But we also have to restore
Yuba as quickly as possible.
It's an important crossroad in the West.
And don't forget, we still need to repair
all the canals along the Century River.
But what about the casino?
It'll be closed.
Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
Um, why's he getting special treatment?
Because Princess Vivi told us to, I guess.
He wants to join the
Supersonic Duck Squadron.
He's a camel.
What gave it away?
Well, I'm off. Thank you. For everything.
Too hasty for your own good, huh?
Someone with your injury
shouldn't even be out of bed.
I'll be fine.
Just promise me that if you make it
home, you'll take things easy and rest.
Okay, I get it.
Hey, wait.
Here, you forgot this.
Now, Karoo.
Let's go!
To Alubarna.
Hey, Captain Smoker.
Tashigi.
So how are your legs?
They're doing fine. Change the subject.
Thank you.
I saw the new bounties on their heads.
It amounts no surprise
considering the catch.
Have you heard what his
swordsman buddy did?
You mean Roronoa?
He cut down 100 bounty
hunters in Whiskey Peak.
And then, in Alubarna,
he killed Das Bones.
The assassin? No way!
He used to be a bounty hunter and
was known throughout the West Blue.
In Baroque Works, he went
by the alias, Mr. One.
Considering Crocodile had so many
famous warriors at his command,
you'd think they'd be unstoppable
against any opposition.
However, fate was not kind.
One day, we'll have a rematch.
Damn Straw Hats.
And I will defeat you, Roro no Azoro.
Looks like the Marines
have stopped following us.
That's good news.
We shook him off.
Stop it!
What's with the pathetic groans?
I miss her!
That's enough whining.
If you wanted her to join that bad,
then you shouldn't have let her leave.
You savage! Lockhead! Idiot.
Three-sword style.
Saying three-sword style
isn't an insult, Luffy.
Four-sword style.
It's not the number that's the problem.
An effective insult must
involve some personal
detail about the recipient
that's rude or disparaging.
Looks like we finally
escaped the firing squad.
Yeah.
Excellent work.
Here to avenge your friends, just try it.
What the hell are you doing here?
Horny!
Who's she?
I don't know, but she's so damn beautiful.
Didn't I tell you before?
Don't point such dangerous objects at me!
Are you always so slow?
How long have you been on our ship?
Quite a while.
These are your clothes, right?
I'm borrowing them.
Just a minute, lady!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Monkey D. Luffy!
It hasn't been so long.
that you've forgotten what
you did to me, has it?
Me?
What did you do to that beautiful
woman, you lousy bastard?
Tell me!
All stowways must leave the
ship immediately. Me, I'll...
Wait a minute. Stop lying.
You know I didn't do anything to you.
Wrong.
And what you did to me was unbearable.
Go ahead. Admit it.
Who's that woman?
And what's she talking about?
It's time that all
mystery chicks vacate the
ship or will be forced
to call the Marines.
Thank you for voyaging
on the going barrier.
Tear you apart!
You're not making any sense.
What do you want me to do?
I want to join you. What?
Use that. Immediately.
It can neutralize the poison
from Crocodile's hook.
Even if he was buried in this rubble,
there's a chance he might survive
since he's actually rubber.
You looked me straight
in the eye and told me
that the only thing
written here was history.
Why did you lie to me?
You knew?
How cruel.
The truth is, this country's history
isn't written anywhere in there.
Instead, it has everything about the
weapon you wanted to get your hands on.
The description, location.
It doesn't make any sense.
If you had told Crocodile
this information,
this country would now
be his for the taking.
Isn't that right?
I'm not interested whether
people in this country
live or die it really
makes no difference to me
I had already decided
from the start not to give
Crocodile the weapon I
don't understand but why did
you come here I don't
really know anymore chasing
a dream I suppose an empty
dream the last remaining
poneglyph in the world
that still carries the
true history the real
poneglyph what do you mean by
the true history nothing it
doesn't matter now for 20 years
i've searched and i've never had
a better lead than this this is
my last hope and it didn't work
out so if i'm going to die here
it's the perfect time i'm tired
of this fool's crusade it's over
all i wanted was to learn our true history
and to share it with
the whole world so then
you're saying that it's possible our lost
history could actually
be uncovered and the
poneglyphs are the key to
unlocking these records?
You mean, all this time?
Okay, let's go. Hold on.
I no longer have a reason to live.
Just leave me here.
You're coming with me.
Do what you want once we're out of here.
I wanted nothing more than
to die at that very moment.
But you forced me to live.
That's your crime.
There's no place for me to go.
Or return to so i've
decided that i'll join you
i see your problem guess
there's no other choice.
Welcome there's nothing to worry
about trust me she isn't a bad person.
Pay attention i want some straight up and
honest answers i'll ask
you one more time what's
your name uh my name's
usa hello nico robin
okay nico robin so what's your occupation
archaeologist are you serious archaeology
runs in my blood i come
from a long line of
It was when I was eight years old that I
decided to pursue archaeology as my career.
Shortly thereafter, I found myself
wanted by the world government.
Since then, I've spent the past
20 years hiding from the world.
You've been alone?
Ever since you were eight?
Then one day, I heard
the calling of the sea,
but there's no way for a child
to survive alone on the water.
The only option I found
that ensured my protection
and the ability to achieve my goal was...
I chose to work for various rogues,
not an ideal solution, but
it brought me this far.
And here we are.
I'm good at maneuvering through
obstacles to achieve a goal.
I'd be a great asset to
you and your friends.
Huh.
You're full of confidence.
What's your specialty?
Killing.
Sophie!
My investigation has concluded
that she is far too dangerous!
You guys listening to me!
Seriously.
I'm disappointed.
You two are pathetic.
Until recently, she was the vice
president of a crime syndicate.
And you really think such
a woman should join us?
You may have fooled these
idiots, but I'm not convinced.
You pull anything, and I'll
personally kick you out.
All right.
I'll keep that in mind.
Oh, I just remembered.
I brought along some of
Crocodile's jewelry with me.
Wow, I love you, sister.
You're the best.
Oh, boy, here we go.
Nami's been had.
It's Chick's bad news.
She's following her lead
like some kind of pet.
Oh, love. Bold.
The likes of which I've never seen.
I'm captured by your spell.
Held prisoner in your eyes.
Treasure.
I was driftwood floating at sea until you
struck me like a thunderbolt
igniting my soul.
A snack.
Oh, thank you.
Look at him falling all over himself.
Yeah, well, he was a lost
cause from the start.
Looks like you and I are the only
holdouts on this ship of insanity.
We shouldn't blame the others.
Their simple minds
can't resist her charge.
Hey, Usa!
Chopper!
What should I call you, Robin?
Or something more daring
that declares my love?
Leaving?
She's great!
With an adult charm!
She's far different than Nami!
This ship has charm.
Is it always this lively?
Yeah, it usually is.
This woman's up to something. But what?
What's the forecast, Navigator?
Is it smooth sailing ahead?
The wind is calm and
the weather's beautiful.
There's no problems on my end, sis.
How would you know?
You haven't stopped
gawking at that jewelry.
Anji, is our snack ready? Be patient.